kulfoto.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Notice

1\. Personal Information

**Browsing KULfoto.com:** You can watch photos on KULfoto.com without registering your Facebook or Twitter account with KULfoto.com. You also can contact us through the KULfoto.com contact form without having to register your Facebook or Twitter account with KULfoto.com.

**Your KULfoto.com Account:** For some activities on KULfoto.com, like uploading photos, flagging photos, or watching restricted photos, you need a Facebook or Twitter account registered with KULfoto.com. We ask only for your public Facebook or Twitter personal information (only the information you share on Facebook or Twitter with everyone) when you register your Facebook or Twitter account. 

**Usage Information:** When you use KULfoto.com, we may record information about your usage of the site. If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your KULfoto.com Account. 

**Content Uploaded to Site:** Any personal information or photo content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., photo comments) may be collected and used by others. 

2\. Uses

If you register your Facebook or Twitter account with KULfoto.com, we may use the information you share with everyone to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of KULfoto.com, and to process any flagging activity or other communication you send to us. 

We do not collect your email address and we do not use your personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. 

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit KULfoto.com; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests; (f) cookie that collects anonymous traffic data. 

3\. Information That is Publicly Available

When you register your Facebook or Twitter account with KULfoto.com, NONE of the information about your KULfoto.com Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of KULfoto.com not including your activity using Facebook Social Plugins.

Your KULfoto.com Account name, NOT your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on KULfoto.com, such as when you send messages through Facebook Social Plugins on KULfoto.com. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site. 

Any photos that you submit to Daily Photo Feed on KULfoto.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other KULfoto.com users or the general public. Your Anonymous Nickname could be displayed next to these photos in some cases.

Any photos that you submit to the albums you have created on KULfoto.com WILL NOT be redistributed and KULfoto.com WILL NOT provide access to these photos to any other users. KULfoto.com will allow access to these photos ONLY through unique valid Share Links which you can share with other people. In case of using Share Links, your Anonymous Nickname or KULfoto.com Account name could be displayed next to the content.

All photos that you submit to your albums on KULfoto.com are considered private and KULfoto.com WILL NEVER share your Share Links with anyone.

4\. Your Choices

You may, of course, decline to register your Facebook or Twitter account with KULfoto.com, in which case you can still view photos and explore KULfoto.com, but KULfoto.com may not be able to provide certain services to you. Some KULfoto.com features may use Google services like AdSense. The privacy notices of those services govern the use of your personal information associated with them. 

5\. Advertising on KULfoto.com

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit KULfoto.com website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://networkadvertising.org/)

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to KULfoto.com website.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to the visitors of KULfoto.com website based on their visit to KULfoto.com site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the advertising [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Other third-party ad serving companies may display ads on KULfoto.com. KULfoto.com does not provide any personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. KULfoto.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with KULfoto.com is maintained and dealt with by KULfoto.com in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Dated: November 22, 2013**
